[Nanako] Long time no see, Kasuga.
I guess it's been...
three years now? [chuckles]
It's so crazy bumping into you like this!
Ah...
Yeah.
-Nanako?
-Yes?
Who is this?
Just a classmate from junior high.
I'm on my way to a concert
with my boyfriend. Aren't we?
-[boyfriend] Yep.
-[Nanako chuckles]
[Takao] I see...
Ah.
Hey, I know.
Let's exchange contact info.
Sure.
[Nanako] Let me see...
There we go.
I'll send a text just in case.
Sent.
[phone chimes]
[Nanako] Good.
CAN WE TALK? HOW'S THIS WEEKEND?
See you around, then.
-Let's go. [chuckles softly]
-[boyfriend] Sure.
[♪ opening theme music playing]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 10
[indistinct chatter]
-Hi ya!
-[groans]
-[Aya giggles]
-[breathing heavily]
[Aya] I'm so sleepy.
I couldn't fall asleep at all last night.
I ended up working on the prologue.
Nice.
[Aya] The thing is,
I want to ask for a favor.
I've decided not to read other books
until I finish writing mine.
So, I want you to hold on to this for me.
Kasuga, did something happen between you
and that girl we met last night?
[Takao] Not really...
We were just in the same homeroom class.
[bell ringing]
Okay, then. I'll keep this safe.
[Nanako] What's wrong with you?
STYLE
::cue()
I know.
Did I upset your girlfriend
by suggesting we meet?
Tokiwa and I aren't dating or anything.
You're not?
Look, they have pizza, too!
So many choices.
[exclaims] The food's great, isn't it?
Saeki,
how have you been doing... since then?
[groans softly] I don't
remember very well.
I was in Juvenile Detention
for about a month,
and then we moved to Utsunomiya.
But, really, I don't remember much.
I've made friends in high school, though.
I have a boyfriend now, too.
So...
I guess I'm happy and stuff.
I see.
Yeah.
How about you, Kasuga?
After what happened...
How have you been doing?
Kasuga,
are you happy right now?
What about Nakamura?
After that...
How has she been doing?
I don't know.
I haven't seen her since.
I don't even know where she is now.
[Nanako] Why?
Why don't you know
what happened to Nakamura?
You were trying to die together, right?
But Nakamura pushed you away.
That's what it looked like to me.
Am I wrong?
Why do you think she did that?
Why did Nakamura shove you, Kasuga?
Don't you know?
When I saw that...
I thought, "Serves you right."
Watching you two fail to die,
being forced to live miserably...
I started laughing uncontrollably.
If you two had died that day,
I would have been so frustrated,
I might have lost my mind.
I...
Even though I did that...
I don't feel like dying anymore.
Tokiwa, was it?
Do you...
like her?
I...
I want to read the novel she writes.
She let me read the plot,
and it was really interesting.
She's writing that novel now,
STYLE
::cue()
-and I...
-Liar.
Are you going to make her miserable, too?
She's a replacement for Nakamura.
A tool to make you feel better.
You're wrong.
[Nanako] You haven't changed at all.
You use people any way you please,
and throw them out
when it becomes too much.
[Takao bangs table]
That's not true.
It is.
Just watch.
I know,
because that girl isn't Nakamura.
You can't face anyone other than Nakamura.
So, you end up having to throw them out.
[♪ tense music playing]
Then again...
You never actually faced Nakamura either,
did you?
You just kept running away the whole time.
Running away from everything.
I knew.
I knew that would happen.
Still...
I'm disappointed.
Excuse me, I'd like to pay now.
[Takao sobbing]
[phone ringing]
[line ringing]
[flips phone shut]
[sighs]
[phone vibrating]
KOJI
[Aya] Were you busy this weekend?
You didn't take any of my calls.
Was it about the novel?
[Aya] Once I started writing, I dunno...
There wasn't much there, I guess.
I'm disappointed.
I didn't know my writing was this bad.
Don't say that.
Actually...
Koji's been asking to make up,
and he says
he also wants to apologize to you, Kasuga.
But, you don't want
to see him again... right?
STYLE
::cue()
[Koji] I'm sorry for the other day!
I was out of line.
Koji, please keep it down.
[Takao] No, I'm the one who should--
No!
I'm really sorry
for saying those nasty things.
To be honest, that day,
I thought you might take Aya from me,
and that's all I could think about.
I'm sorry to you, too, Aya!
-I'll change!
-Hey, Koji?
Can you just...
Ah...
If anything, I feel more confident
after overcoming this crisis with you.
Really? Did you learn your lesson?
[Koji] I swear!
Could you... accept my apology?
[Koji sighs]
I really appreciate it!
-I'll call you!
-[Aya] See you.
-You too, Kasuga! See you around.
-[Aya] Sure.
Koji, over here.
-Get back to work, please.
-[Koji] Ah.
[Aya] Kasuga,
you must think...
I'm an idiot, right?
What?
Why would you say that?
[Aya] No reason.
[Takao] Tokiwa!
What is it?
[exhales]
Sorry.
It's nothing. Forget it.
DECEMBER 24TH
[student 1] It's December 24th.
What comes to mind?
[student 2] Santa!
-[student 1] Snow!
-[indistinct chatter]
[student 2] Reindeer!
Sleighs!
-Presents!
-[exclaims]
[student 1] Fir tree!
[Koji] Aya!
[Aya] You're so loud.
-Why did you come through the gate?
-[Koji laughing]
-I'm tired of waiting!
-[Aya chuckles]
[Koji] Why do you have work today,
of all days?
-[Aya] I told you.
-[Koji chuckles]
[electricity crackling]
[clattering]
[Takao's shadow]
You haven't changed a bit.
You don't actually want
to read Tokiwa's novel.
You just want to be the person
who got to read it.
Isn't that right?
That's not true.
[Takao's shadow]
You're just like a parasite.
It used to be on books,
then on Saeki,
then on Nakamura.
And next,
you're going to use Tokiwa and her novel
for yourself.
You're wrong!
[Takao's shadow] Then why did
Nakamura shove you away?
Why do you not understand?
It's because you didn't try
to face anybody!
You're the one who destroyed it all.
You destroyed Saeki,
you destroyed your family,
and you destroyed Nakamura, too.
[♪ eerie music playing]
[Takao] That's not true...
The person Nakamura was back then is gone.
[♪ gentle music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
She doesn't exist
anywhere in this world.
It's true.
It's all true.
I...
hurt and broke Nakamura and everyone else.
I might never be forgiven for what I did.
But, still...
Still, the person I need to be facing now,
in this moment, is...
Kasuga,
you must think...
I'm an idiot, right?
Tokiwa,
you've been suffering all alone.
This whole time,
you've suppressed your true self...
[wind howling]
I can't do that.
I can't keep living
in the world as a ghost!
[squelching]
[wind stops blowing]
[Takao inhales]
[door opens]
[Aya] Here you go.
-[door opens]
-[wind chimes tinkling]
-Welcome!
-[Koji] Welcome!
[Takao panting]
Tokiwa...
I love you!
Please go out with me!
[laughing]
Hey!
What kind of joke is this?
And on Christmas Eve, of all days?
Calm down for a minute. Have a seat.
[Takao] Tokiwa.
Wait a second.
I'm on the clock right now.
I'll be taking a break soon, so...
Tokiwa.
Come to me.
I want you in my life!
I'll kill your ghost for you.
Let's get off
these tracks.
I'm in love with you!
Seriously, what's gotten into you?
Sorry for the commotion, everyone.
-Hey.
-Tokiwa.
-Tokiwa!
-[Koji] Drop it already!
You're causing trouble!
Koji...
I'm sorry.
What?
[♪ pleasant music playing]
What do you mean by "sorry"?
Manager...
-What?
-[Aya] I'm sorry.
I'll be quitting as of today.
[manager] What the... Quit? Aya?
-[door opens]
-[wind chimes tinkling]
Manager...
Do you mind if I go on break?
STYLE
::cue()
[both panting]
[Takao chuckling]
[Aya chuckles]
I forgot my bag.
[Takao exclaims softly]
[Aya] And this apron...
I'll have to wash it and give it back.
Sorry...
[laughing]
[♪ music continues]
[breath trembling]
So warm.
[both laughing]
FINAL CHAPTER
Kasuga!
[exclaims] I didn't look, I promise!
When do I get to read it, though?
Soon.
Just as soon as I'm done writing.
[♪ soft music playing]
[keyboard clacking]
[indistinct chatter]
[Aya] Beautiful, isn't it?
[Takao] Yeah.
STYLE
::cue()
Is it really okay?
Is it really okay for me to be this happy?
[Aya] What was that?
I'm happy too, you know?
That reminds me.
There's somewhere I want to go
during spring break.
Where?
The town you were born in.
I want to see it.
There's nothing to see.
It's just a plain old, rural town.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
-[door opens]
-Welcome home.
[Shizue] Welcome home.
Grandpa's been taken to the hospital?
It's not looking too good.
Mom and I will go see him tomorrow.
You can stay here, Takao.
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[squelching]
I'm coming with you.
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing theme music playing]
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
[narrator] Kasuga is dragged back
to his past after seeing Saeki again.
He visits his hometown
for the first time in three years.
Next, on Episode 11,
Kasuga finally finds a lead
that could help him find Nakamura.
Translated by Yuka Kristi